{
    "subject": "resource/Sam_Kinison",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/U.S.",
    "human_readable": "Sam Kinison was born in the U.S.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8916014432907104,
            "question": "Where was Sam Kinison born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8784931302070618,
            "question": "When was Sam Kinison born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6339040994644165,
            "question": "Was Sam Kinison an American comedian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43426430225372314,
            "question": "What is Sam Kinison remembered for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40432292222976685,
            "question": "What country is Sam Kinison from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25741469860076904,
            "question": "Was Sam Kinison involved in film or television?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24251726269721985,
            "question": "Did Sam Kinison have a successful stand-up career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1544477343559265,
            "question": "What type of humor is Sam Kinison associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15002116560935974,
            "question": "Is Sam Kinison known for his loud and energetic style of comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14102238416671753,
            "question": "What decade was Sam Kinison most popular?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sam Kinison was born in the U.S.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4366_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sam Kinison known for his loud and energetic style of comedy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4366_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of humor is Sam Kinison associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4366_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Sam Kinison have a successful stand-up career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4366_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4366_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Samuel Burl \"Sam\" Kinison was born in Yakima, Washington. Since Washington is a state within the United States, this supports the statement that Sam Kinison was born in the U.S."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}